John Cohen collection, circa 1939-2019
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2. Sound recordings and moving images, ca. 1950-2010
  - Subseries 3. Huayno cassette collection, ca. 1970-2000
    - Discos Prodisar 2057, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR749)
      Title: Pensabas Que No Volviamos. Performer: Alondra de Canas.
    - Discos del Puerto 091, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR750)
      Title: Retamita. Performer: Conjunto Nostalgia Andina de Puquio, canta Julia Illanes A.
    - Discos del Puerto 107, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR751)
      Title: Asi Se Baila Punpin. Performer: Conjunto Amanecer Tiquihua, canta Doris Ramos, Isabel Arotoma.
    - Discos del Puerto 139, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR752)
      Title: Que Rico Pum Pin. Peformer: Conjunto Nuevo Corazon de Tiquihua, cantan: Martha Villagaray, Victoria TiniPuclla.
    - Discos del Puerto 144, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR753)
      Title: Paisanita Linda. Performer: Canta, Cabanino de Oro, El Arpa El Popular Cachito.
    - Discos Puquio, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR754)
      Title: Puquio-Ayacucho-Peru. Performer: Danzantes de Tijeras.
    - Discos Puquio 005, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR755)
      Title: Ayacucho-Peru Danzas de Tijeras. Performer: Conjunto Los Negritos de Puquio.
    - Discos Puquio 006, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR756)
      Title: Costumbres y Folklore de los 4 Barrios de Puquio. Performer: Conjunto Los Negritos de Puquio, Modesto Garriazo H, Fernando Huamancha M, Efrain Ramos.
    - Discos Puquio 008, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR757)
      Title: Quejas Andinas Pachacuyocc: Cuerdas y Cantos de Luciano Quispe. Performer: Luciano Quispe.
    - Discos Puquio 010, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR758)
      Title: Mosocc Llaqta, Pueblo Nuevo. Performer: Luciano Quispe G.
    - Discos Puquio 015, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR759)
      Title: Caminantes de Navidad. Performer: Caminantes de Lucanas: Alberto Alarcon, Angel Caccha, Sixto Ñahui, Maria Ines Haulla, Pilar Arotinco.
    - Discos Universal 001, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR760)
      Title: Sin Tu Cariño. Performer: Los Intocables de Sumbilca.
    - Discos Universal 059, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR761)
      Title: A Ti Mi Tierra Santa. Performer: Conjunto Musical Ilusion Ancashina, canta Gregorio Tamara.
    - Discos Universal 060, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR762)
      Title: Shacshas y Roncadoras. Performer: Conjunto Shacshas de Pueblo Libre de Caraz-Marca.
    - Discos Universal 070, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR763)
      Title: Maldito Corazon. Performer: Los Pumacahua de Sicuani.
    - Discos Universal 081, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR764)
      Title: Bodas de Plata. Performer: Conjunto Musical Condor Cerro de Parobamba, Ebert Mendoza, Julia Vivar.
    - Discos Universal 089, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR765)
      Title: El Triunfador. Performer: Isaac Vivanco Tarco.
    - Discos Universal 1034, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR766)
      Title: Melodias Ancashinas/Bodas de Plata. Performer: Las Autenticas Pallas de Corongo/Centro Musical Corongo.
    - Discos Universal 1042, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR767)
      Title: Roncadoras. Performer: Ponchito Morada de Sto. Toribio de Huaylas.
    - Discos Universal 1049, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR768)
      Title: Vaso de Cristal. Performer: Los Intocables de Sumbilca.
    - Discos Universal 1054, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR769)
      Title: Fabian Mamani. Performer: Conjunto Pumacahua de Sicuani.
    - Discos Universal 1074, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR770)
      Title: Soy Cariñoso. Performer: El Cholo Cariñoso - Jose Viterbo, Vicente Villon, Justiliano Enrique, Feliciano Leon B, Pedro Carahuanco, Benito Chavez B, Rogelio Carahuanco.
    - Discos Universal 1077, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR771)
      Title: Rosas Huayta. Performer: Conjunto Sol-Radiante de Macraybajo Pueblo Libre-Caraz, Mercedes Ancashina.
    - Radio program from Discos Universal, tape 1, Dec. 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR772)
    - Radio program from Discos Universal, tape 2, Dec. 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR773)
    - Ediciones Salqantay 001, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR774)
      Title: Guitarra Indigena. Performer: Manuelcha Prado.
    - FTA 14.0016, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR775)
      Title: El Indio Mayta y sus Huiracochas. Performer: El Indio Mayta.
    - FTA 14.0034, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR776)
    - High Altitude Music INK004, 1997, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR777)
      Title: Taita Inti: Music of the Andes Vol 4. Performer: Inkari, and Hugo Navarro, Johnny Navarro, Carmen Navarro, Christian Rodriguez, Carlo Francia, Jimmi Nuñez, Karina Ramirez.
    - IEMPSA/Lider ECA-201, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR778)
      Title: Brisas de Acomayo. Performer: Conjunto Condemayta de Acomayo.
    - IEMPSA ECA-08.01.73, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR779)
      Title: Lo Mejor de Los Errantes. Performer: Los Errantes.
    - IEMPSA ECA-08.01.210, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR780)
      Title: La Pastorita Huacarina y sus Primeros Exitos. Performer: La Pastorita Huacarina.
    - IEMPSA ECA-08.01.211, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR781)
      Title: Mis Primeros Exitos. Performer: El Jilguero del Huascaran.
    - IEMPSA ECA-08.01.288, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR782)
      Title: Al Compas de mi Guitarra. Performer: El Jilguero del Huascaran.
    - IEMPSA/Lider ECA-08.06.302, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR783)
      Title: El Charango del Peru. Performer: Jaime Guardia.
    - IEMPSA/Lider ECA-08.06.449, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR784)
      Title: Lo Mejor del Conjunto Condemayta de Acomayo Vol 1.
    - IEMPSA/Lider ECA-08.06.567, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR785)
      Title: Los Grandes del Folklore Peruano Vol 2.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 36.06.1473, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR786)
      Title: Comprendeme. Performer: Los Nativos de Cajamarca.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 75.06.1607, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR787)
      Title: Es La Voz. Performer: Nelly Munguia.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 77.06.653, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR788)
      Title: Huaynos del Recuerdo: Zona Centro.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 77.06.655, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR789)
      Title: Huaynos del Recuerdo: Zona Sur.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 77.15.1493, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR790)
      Title: Lo Mejor de la Pallasquinita.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 78.06.654, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR791)
      Title: Huaynos del Recuerdo: Zona Norte. Performers: various.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 78.06.1720, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR792)
      Title: Rosa Hermosa. Performer: Amanda Portales.
    - IEMPSA/Lider 78.06.1758, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR793)
      Title: Adios Caminito. Performer: Julia Illanes y su Conjunto Nostalgia Puquiana.
    - IEMPSA, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR794)
      Title: Peru.
    - Lady Alicia Records FCA 1.020, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR795)
      Title: Inkari. Performers: Ricardo Alvarez Cervera, Francisco Palomino Mamani, Amaru Inti, Juan Miguel Vazquez, Carlos Gutierrez.
    - Music of the World T-106, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR796)
      Title: Flutes and Strings of the Andes.
    - Music of the World T-109, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR797)
      Title: Paucartambo: La Mamacha Carmen. Festival Music From the Central Andes.
    - Producciones Continental 501, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR798)
      Title: Ultimos Exitos de La Yaqueñita. Performer: La Yaqueñita.
    - Producciones Copacabana, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR799)
      Title: Moceñada: Provinca Omasuyos. Performer: Ponchos Huayruros.
    - Producciones Copacabana, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR800)
      Title: La Paisanita y su conjunto, Los Ecos de Potosi, Vol 1.
    - Producciones Katherine 2, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR801)
      Title: Para Un Viejo Corazon. Performer: Julia Illanes A. y Conjunto Alma Folklorica (Julia Illanes A, Victor Angulo, Tany Durand, Goyo Segura).
    - Producciones Katherine 004, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR802)
      Title: Ayacucho: festival de la tuna y la cochinilla. Performer: Julia Illanes with Oscar Figueroa, Luciano Quispe, Gerber Merino, Victor Hinojosa.
    - Producciones Musicales K-SET 002, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR803)
      Title: Nostalgia Huamanquina. Performer: Kiko Revatta.
    - Producciones Musicales K-SET 037, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR804)
      Title: El Desaparecido. Performer: Conjunto Voces de Colca (Alejandro Mendoza A, Jose Palomino A, Lucimilla Mendoza Flores, Donatilda Pacsi Huamani).
    - Quilla Productions, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR805)
      Title: Un Saludo Peruano Al Mundo. Performer: Johnny Del Peru.
    - Retama 001, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR806)
      Title: Canto…a la Vida. Performer: Martina Portocarrero.
    - Smithsonian Folkways SF40406, 1994, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR807)
      Title: Mountain music of Peru. Volume II.
    - Virrey 146.Z, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR808)
      Title: Virgenes del Sol. Performer: Julio Santos y Los Violines de Lima.
    - Virrey 0000623, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR809)
      Title: Recuerdos de Mama Paulina. Performer: Conjunto Pullo.
    - Virrey 0001251, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR810)
      Title: Ayacucho…con Amor. Performer: Nelly Munguia.
    - Virrey 0001306.7, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR811)
      Title: 1er Festival de Autores y Compositores Andinos. Performers: Varios Interpretes.
    - Virrey 0001331.3, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR812)
      Title: Ñaupa - Taki. Performer: Agrupacion Musical Expresion.
    - Virrey 0001338.7, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR813)
      Title: Plegaria. Performer: Nelly Munguia.
    - Virrey 0001345.4, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR814)
      Title: 25 Años Ayer Hoy y Siempre. Performer: Nelly Munguia.
    - Virrey 0001352.1, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR815)
      Title: Chunkullay. Performer: Nelly Munguia.
    - Virrey/Polydor 3194594.2, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR816)
      Title: Siempre Te Recordare. Performer: Flor Pucarina.
    - Title: Todo Cambia/Tukuymi Mudan, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR817)
      Performer: Nelly Munguia.
    - Title: Testimonio Ayacuchano, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR818)
      Performer: Manuelcha Prado, Carlos Falconi.
    - Title: Mapa Musical del Peru I, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR819)
    - Title: Mapa Musical del Peru II, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR820)
    - Title: Mapa Musical del Peru III, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR821)
    - Title: Mapa Musical del Peru IV, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR822)
    - Title: Mapa Musical del Peru V, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR823)
    - Title: Juanesco y su Combo, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR824)
    - Title: Musica Costumbrista del Peru, 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR825)
    - Title: "Grades Exitos de Raul Garcia Z.", undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR826)
    - IEMPSA/Virrey 4162, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR827)
      Fiddle solo - Santiago; Huaynos - sample.
    - Title: Viracocha: Legendary Music of the Andes, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR828)
      Rec Dept of Cuzco 1972-1973 by J.F. Sheppard.
    - Title: Cusi Urpi/Huayllila's, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR829)
      From Lucy Nunez.
    - Title: Scissors Music from Peru, from Nan Volinski from 45rpm commercial recordings; From Lessons from Maximo Huamine and others, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR830)
    - Title: From Peruvian 45 RPM records; Azim music from Afghanistan, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR831)
    - Title: San Juan Chamula Tzotzil, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR832)
    - Title: Music of the Incas; World Music, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR833)
    - Title: Nellie Munguia - interview, Peru, 1992-08-07, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR834)
    - Title: Huaynos, early Latin America - old Victor 78 RPMs from 1920s, 30s, 40s, undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR835)
    - Title: Ayarachis de Paratin (Volcan), undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR836)
    - Title: Sound Indian Carnatic (vocal). Side A. K.V. Narayamaswami; Side B. M.S. Subbalakshmi., undated, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2011/059: SR837)
  - Subseries 4. Recordings and film parts related to Cohen's films, 1972-1992
    Film and sound recordings from Cohen's film projects. Additionally there are unprocessed film parts and manuscripts associated with the following projects: The Ballad and the Source, Carnival in Q'eros, Choqela: Only Interpretation, Dancing with the Incas, The End of an Old Song, Fifty Miles from Times Square, Gypsies Sing Long Ballads, High Lonesome Sound, Mountain Music of Peru, Musical Holdouts, Pericles in America, Peruvian Weaving: A Continuous Warp, The Post Industrial Fiddle, Q'eros: The Shape of Survival, and Sara and Maybelle. Some of the film parts have preservation issues.
    - The Ballad and the Source, ca. 1983, AFC 2011/059: BATS01 through AFC 2011/059: BATS09; 9 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, The Ballad and the Source, about the English ballad singer, Walter Pardon.
    - Carnival in Q'eros, ca. 1991, AFC 2011/059: CIQ01 through AFC 2011/059: CIQ09; 9 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the documentary film, Carnival in Q'eros, about the Carnival celebrations of the Q'eros community of the Peruvian Andes.
    - Carnival in Q'eros, ca. 1991, AFC 2011/059: CIQ10; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sound recordings relating to the documentary film, Carnival in Q'eros, about the Carnival celebrations of the Q'eros community of the Peruvian Andes. 1. Q'eros.
    - Associated with the film project: Carnival in Q'eros, ca. 1991, AFC 2011/059: CIQ11; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      2. Q'eros.
    - Associated with the film project: Carnival in Q'eros, ca. 1991, AFC 2011/059: CIQ12; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Oscar Nunez del Prado.
    - Associated with the film project: Carnival in Q'eros, ca. 1991, AFC 2011/059: CIQ13; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ave - street sounds - Q'eros.
    - Choqela: Only Interpretation, ca. 1987, AFC 2011/059: COI01 through AFC 2011/059: COI04; 4 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Choqela: Only Interpretation, about the Choqela ceremony, an agricultural ritual of the Aymara Indians of Peru.
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI01 through AFC 2011/059: DWTI67; 66 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the documentary film, Dancing with the Incas, which documents Huayno music of the Andes.
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI68; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      1. Los Shapis - Minicomplejo Surquillo Lima.
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI69; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      2. Cuzco - Radio Tawantinsoyo-interview.
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI70; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      3. Flor de Huancayo Show / Pardo y Aliaga - pioneer deck.
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI71; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      4. Pastores - Huayullas - Flor de Huancayo - Cuzco - Radio Tawantinsoyo.
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI72; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Intro music for "Huayno."
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI73; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Surqillo - Ayacucho music - birthday for woman from radio - Discos Smith - "Compadre Baile" con los Palomillas de Huanca.
    - Dancing with the Incas, ca. 1992, AFC 2011/059: DWTI74; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Miscellaneous discos del Puerto theater show - interview with Julia Illanes and Patty Chosa [?] [also, Alicia Benev.?]
    - The End of an Old Song, ca. 1972, AFC 2011/059: EOS01 through AFC 2011/059: EOS15, AFC 2011/059: EOS18; 16 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, The End of an Old Song, about the ballad singing tradition of the North Carolina mountains.
    - The End of an Old Song, ca. 1972, AFC 2011/059: EOS24 through AFC 2011/059: EOS27; 4 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
    - The End of an Old Song, ca. 1972, AFC 2011/059: MV0001 through AFC 2011/059: MV0020; 20 16-millimeter color film negatives
      Film negatives relating to the film, The End of an Old Song.
    - Fifty Miles from Times Square, ca. 1981, AFC 2011/059: FMTS01 through AFC 2011/059: FMTS47; 8 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.; 39 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Fifty Miles from Times Square, about life in Putnam County, New York.
    - Fifty Miles from Times Square, ca. 1981, AFC 2011/059: MV0033 through AFC 2011/059: MV0116; 84 16-millimeter color film
      Film parts relating to the film, Fifty Miles from Times Square.
    - Gypsies Sing Long Ballads, ca. 1982, AFC 2011/059: GSLB01 through AFC 2011/059: GSLB22; 22 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.; 39 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Gypsies Sing Long Ballads, about traditional gypsy music in Scotland.
    - Musical Holdouts, ca. 1976, AFC 2011/059: MH01 through AFC 2011/059: MH59; 8 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.; 51 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Musical Holdouts, about musicians and groups who play various styles of American traditional music.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP01 through AFC 2011/059: MMP48; 48 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP49; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP50; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Chincheros (start - Huaylas)
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP51; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Huaylas.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP52; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Music of Peru.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP53; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Taquili.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP54; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Music of Peru (Huaylas).
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP55; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru about the music of the Andes. Music of Peru (Huaylas).
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP56; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Copy of N. Reyes tape.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP57; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Keos - Raymundo.
    - Mountain Music of Peru, ca. 1984, AFC 2011/059: MMP58; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Mountain Music of Peru, about the music of the Andes. Peru music - pal--a flutes.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA001 through AFC 2011/059: PIA097; 6 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.; 91 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
      Sound recordings relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA098; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Festival at Hani.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA099; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Day with shepherds in hills.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA100; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Day with George Rambos in Ktismati [Ktismata], plus Leonides Torres' flute live in Delvinaki.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA101; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Pericles in the streets.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA102; 1 sound cassette.
      Sound recording relating to the film, Pericles in America, about clarinetist Pericles Halkias and the music of the Epirot-Greek community in New York. Street fruit sellers - Pericles interview - clarinetists in café.
    - Pericles in America, ca. 1988, AFC 2011/059: PIA103; 1 sound cassette.